McKelvey, Jean T. Papers /3001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Cases 517-546 (Box 109)
  - Local 600, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 529, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 530, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 531, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 532, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 533, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 534, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 534, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 535, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 535, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 536, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 536, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 537, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 538, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 539, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 540, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 30)
  - PRB Case 541, 1980-1981 (Box 109, Folder 31)
  - PRB Case 542, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 32)
  - PRB Case 543, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 33)
  - PRB Case 544, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 34)
  - PRB Case 544, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 35)
  - PRB Case 545, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 36)
  - PRB Case 545, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 37)
  - PRB Case 546, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 38)
- Cases 547-570 (Box 110)
  - PRB Case 547, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 547, 1980 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 548, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 549, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 550, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 551, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 552, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 552, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 553, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 554, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 555, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 556, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 557, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 558, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 559, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 559, 1980 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 560, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 560, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 561, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 562, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 563, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 564, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 565, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 566, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 566, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 567, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 568, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 569, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 570, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 29)
- Cases 571-592 (Box 111)
  - PRB Case 571, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 572, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 573, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 574, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 576, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 577, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 578, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 579, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 580, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 581, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 582, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 582, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 583, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 583, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 583, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 584, 1981-1982 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 585, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 587, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 586, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 587, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 588, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 589, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 590, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 591, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 592, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 25)
- Cases 593-612 (Box 112)
  - PRB Case 593, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 593, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 594, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 594, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 594, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 595, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 596, 1974 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 597, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 598, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 599, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 600, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 600, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 601, 1981-1982 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 602, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 203, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 604, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 605, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 606, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 607, 1933 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 608, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 609, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 610, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 611, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 612, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 24)
- Cases 613-637 (Box 113)
  - PRB Case 613, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 614, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 615, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 616, 1984 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 616, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 617, 1982 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 618, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 619, 1967 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 620, 1980 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 621, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 622+623, 1982-1983 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 623, 1984 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 623, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 624, 1982 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 625, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 626, 1984 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 626, 1982 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 627, 1982 (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 628, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 629 + 659, 1984 (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 629, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 630, 1984 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 631, 1984 (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 631, 1977-1979 (Box 113, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 632, 1984 (Box 113, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 634, 1984 (Box 113, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 635, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 636, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 637, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 29)
- Cases 638-662 (Box 114)
  - PRB Case 638, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 639, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 640, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 640, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 640, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 641, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 642, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 643, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 644, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 645, 1981-1982 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 646, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 647, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 647, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 648, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 649, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 649, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 650, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 652, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 653, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 654, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 654, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 654, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 655, 1982-1984 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 656, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 656, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 657, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 658, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 659, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 660, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 661, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 30)
  - PRB Case 662, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 31)
- Cases 663-678 (Box 115)
  - PRB Case 663, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 664, 1986 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 665, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 665, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 666, 1981 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 667, 1985 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 668, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 668, 1978-1984 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 669, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 670, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 670, 1981 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 670, 1978-1980 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 670, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 670, 1985 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 670, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 671 + 672, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 671 + 672, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 673, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 675, 1985 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 674, 1982-1984 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 675, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 676, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 677, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 678, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 678, 1981-1982 (Box 115, Folder 25)
- Cases 679-696 (Box 116)
  - PRB Case 679, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 680, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 681, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 682, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 683, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 684, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 685, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 686, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 687+688, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 688, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 688, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 688, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 688, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 689, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 690, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 691, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 692, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 692, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 693, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 693, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 694, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 695, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 696, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 696, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 24)
- Cases 697-731 (Box 117)
  - PRB Case 698, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 699, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 700, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 701, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 702, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 703, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 704, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 705, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 706, 1981 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 707, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 708, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 709, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 711, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 712, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 713, 1983 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 714, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 715, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 716, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 717, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 718+719, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 720, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 721, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 722, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 723, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 724, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 725+726+744, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 725+726+744, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 726, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 726, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 727, 1983 (Box 117, Folder 30)
  - PRB Case 728, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 31)
  - PRB Case 729, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 32)
  - PRB Case 730, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 33)
- Cases 732-761 (Box 118)
  - PRB Case 731+732, 1984 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 732, 1984 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 733, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 734, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 735, 1982-1984 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 736, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 737, 1980 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 738, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 739, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 740, 1982-1987 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 740, 1983-1986 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 741, 1971-1981 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 742, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 743, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 744, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 745, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 746, 1983 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 747, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 748, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 749, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 750, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 751, 1980 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 752, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 753, 1966 (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 754, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 755, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 756, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 757, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 758, 1985-1986 (Box 118, Folder 29)
- Cases 762-786 (Box 119)
  - PRB Case 760, 1984-1987 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 761, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 762, 1986-1987 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 762, 1986-1987 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 763, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 764, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 765, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 766, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 766, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 767, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 768, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 769, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 770, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 771, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 771, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 772, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 773, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 774, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 775, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 776, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 777, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 778, 1984 (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 778, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 779, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 780, 1981 (Box 119, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 781, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 782, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 783, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 784, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 785, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 30)
- Cases 787-805 (Box 120)
  - PRB Case 787, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 787, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 787, 1983-1987 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 787, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 787, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 788, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 789, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 790, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 791, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 792, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 793, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 794, 1980-1985 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 795, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 796, 1976 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 797, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 798, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 799, 1972-1987 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 800, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 801, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 802, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 802, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 802, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 803, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 804, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 805, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 805, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 26)
- Cases 806-830 (Box 121)
  - PRB Case 806, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 807, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 808, 1988-1990 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 808, 1989-1990 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 809, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 810, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 811, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 812, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 813, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 813, 1985 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 814, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 815, 1985 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 815, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 816, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 817, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 817, 1986 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 817, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 818, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 818, 1977 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 819, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 820, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 821, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 822, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 823, 1987-1988 (Box 121, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 824, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 825, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 826, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 826, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 827, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 29)
  - PRB Case 828, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 30)
  - PRB Case 829, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 31)
- Cases 831-852 (Box 122)
  - PRB Case 830, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 831, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 831, 1975 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 832, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 833, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 834, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 835, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 835, 1989 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 835, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 836, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 837, 1987 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 838, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 839, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 840, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 841, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 841, 1986 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 842, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 843, 1989 (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 844, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 844, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 845, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 846, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 847, 1987-1988 (Box 122, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 848, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 849, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 849, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 850, 1989 (Box 122, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 851, 1989 (Box 122, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 852, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 29)
- Cases 853-869 (Box 123)
  - PRB Case 853, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 853, 1987-1989 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 853, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 854, 1976-1985 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 855, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 856, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 857, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 857, 1976 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 857, 1983 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 857, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 858, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 859, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 860, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 861, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 862, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 863, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 864, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 865, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 865, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 865, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 865, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 866, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 687, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 868, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 869, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 869, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 869, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 27)
- Cases 870-890 (Box 124)
  - PRB Case 870, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 871, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 872, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 873, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 874, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 874, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 875, 1988-1989 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 876, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 877, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 877, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 879, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 880, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 881, 1988-1989 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 882, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 883, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 884, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 884, 1975-1989 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 885, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 886, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 887, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 888, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 889, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 890, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 23)
- Cases 891-919 (Box 125)
  - PRB Case 891, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 892, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 893, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 894, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 895, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 896, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 897, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 899, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 899, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 900, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 901, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 902, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 903, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 904, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 905, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 906, 1989 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 907, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 908, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 909, 1986-1990 (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 910, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 911, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 912, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 913, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 914, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 915, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 916, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 917, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 918, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 28)
  - PRB Case 919, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 29)
- Cases 920-942 (Box 126)
  - PRB Case 920, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 920, 1985-1987 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 921, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 922, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 923, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 924, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 925, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 925, 1986-1988 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 926, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 927, 1989 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 928, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 929, 1990 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 930, 1988-1990 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 931, 1988-1990 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 932, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 933, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 934, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 934, 1989-1990 (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 935, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 936, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 937, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 938, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 939, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 939, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 940, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 941, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 942, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 942, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 28)
- Cases 943-966 (Box 127)
  - PRB Case 943, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 944, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 945, 1987-1991 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 946, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 947, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - PRB Case 948, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - PRB Case 949, 1990 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - PRB Case 950, 1986 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - PRB Case 951, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - PRB Case 951, 1951 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - PRB Case 953, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - PRB Case 954, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - PRB Case 954, 1989-1990 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - PRB Case 955, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - PRB Case 955, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - PRB Case 956, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - PRB Case 958, 1989-1992 (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - PRB Case 958, 1989-1991 (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - PRB Case 959, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 19)
  - PRB Case 960, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 20)
  - PRB Case 961, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 21)
  - PRB Case 961, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 22)
  - PRB Case 962, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 23)
  - PRB Case 963, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 24)
  - PRB Case 964, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 25)
  - PRB Case 965, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 26)
  - PRB Case 965, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 27)
  - PRB Case 966, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 28)
- Cases 967-985 (Box 128)
  - PRB Case 967, 1991-1992 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - PRB Case 968, 1992 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - PRB Case 969, 1992 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - PRB Case 970, 1992 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - PRB Case 971, 1992 (Box 128, Folder 5)